沃特工作室
看不见的无法杀死
《透明人：隐形力量2》 即将来袭
《隐形力量2》让我太激动了
Yo, I am so psyched for Invisible Force 2.
拜托 《隐形力量1》很差劲 我喜欢《涨潮》
Please. Invisible Force 1 was lame.
《涨潮》？
I'm all about Rising Tide. Rising Tide? The Deep?
深海？透明人可以打败深海
-Uh-huh. Translucent could kick the Deep's ass.
怎么打败他？透明人可以隐形
How? He's invisible.
他就只有一个本领 就只有这个
That's, like, all he's got. That's it.
正是如此 他悄悄地靠近深海
Exactly. He sneaks up on the Deep,
然后 砰 龟孙子！坐下！
and then boom, motherfucker!
直到深海让一条鲨鱼 咬掉透明人的小鸡鸡
-Sit down. Until the Deep makes a shark bite Translucent's dick off.
他怎能找到透明人的小鸡鸡？ 它也是透明的
How's he gonna find his dick? It's invisible.
不好了
Holy shit.
本吉
Benjy!
起来 快啊 本吉 快！
Get up. Get up, get up, get up. Come on, Benjy. Come on, come on.
别过来 他妈的不要过来
Stay back. Just stay the fuck back.
你在笑什么？
What are you smiling at?
祖国人？
BENJY: Homelander?
你们没事吧？
You boys okay?
我们可以…合影吗？
Can I. . . can I get a selfie?
当然可以
Course you can.
超级七人队的梅芙女王跟祖国人 今天再度英勇救人
ANCHOR: The Seven's Queen Maeve and Homelander
在布鲁克林的街道上 拦截了一辆被挟持的装甲卡车
made another heroic save today, stopping a hijacked armored truck
还留下来 跟一些非常幸运的粉丝合影
on the streets of Brooklyn, then staying behind for a photo op
-吉恩？ 谢谢 珍妮弗 现在…
-with some very lucky fans. Nice to meet you. Jean? Thanks, Jennifer. And now. . .
这算是全功能一体的蓝牙扬声器
HUGHIE: So, this is pretty much everything in one. Bluetooth speakers.
是立体声的 可以装在客厅的任何地方
It's in stereo, so you can put it all around your living room, have some fun with it.
尽情享用它 你说你有个标准的线盒 对吗？
You said you have a standard cable box, right?
好的 那我需要给你弄一个音频转发器 Apt-X编码 低延迟
-Uh-huh. Okay, then I need to get you an audio transmitter,
能减少音频延迟 而且有标准的光纤输入
aptX Low Latency. It makes it so there's less audio lag, and it's got a standard optical in.
就给你选一千兆的高清多媒体界面接口吧 就用这个吧
And let's hook you up with thousand-meg HDMI.
这个稍贵一点 但是碳的传导性好很多
Let's go with this one. Uh, it costs a little bit more, but the carbon's way more conductive.
嘿 加里 我真的需要跟你谈件事
Hey, Gary. Um. . .
以后再谈 小子
-I really need to talk to you about something. Later, kid.
好的
Okay. Cool.
以后再谈…你…
Later you want, like. . . want, like, 30-30 minutes?
是指30分钟？还是45分钟？
Like, a solid 45?
先生 打扰一下
Excuse me, sir?
你好 我想约个时间请你过来
Hi. I'd like to make an appointment
for you to come over and. . .
铺线
lay some cable.
好的 洛缤
Okay. Uh. . . oh, Robin.
亲爱的洛缤
Oh, dear, dear, Robin.
那个词的意思跟你想的不一样
Um, that doesn't mean what you think it means.
“铺线”是指做爱
Um, "laying cable" means sex.
不对 “铺水管”才指做爱
No, "laying pipe" means sex.
“铺线”的意思是你要我去你家
"Laying cable" means you want me to come over to your house
拉一大泡屎
-and just take a big, old shit.
真恶心
-That's disgusting. Well, okay.
好吧 但是你…不过这是谁说的？
But you. . . Who-who said it, though?
好吧 你准备好了吗？
Okay. Are you ready? Despite your best efforts,
尽管你尽了最大努力 我其实还很饿
I'm actually still hungry.
其实我现在更饿了
-I'm actually more hungry now.
我们说了这些撩人的话以后
-Where are we gonna go after all this hot talk? I don't know.
-要去哪里呢？ 不知道
更重要的是 我们之后要去哪里铺线？
-You know? More importantly, where are we gonna go to lay some cable afterwards?
老天爷
Geez.
你问他了吗？
So, did you ask him?
谁？
-Who? Gary.
加里 你向加里要求加薪了吗？
Did you ask Gary for the raise?
对的 今天…今天事特别多
Yeah. Yeah. It was it was a. . .
他超级忙 但是明天一定问 是的
Look, it was a crazy day, and-and he was super busy, but tomorrow for sure. Yes.
好吧
Okay.
我该怎么做？就像祖国人一样踢倒他的门？
What was I supposed to do, kick his door down?
Like Homelander?
我说了“好吧”
I said "okay. "
是的 但你言不由衷
Yeah, but you didn't mean it.
我看到了你的表情 我看见了 少来了
Hey, I see the look. I see it. Come on.
这就像我们刚开始谈恋爱时一样
This is like when we started dating.
我不认为这是真的
I don't think that's. . . I don't think that's true.
老兄 当时是我约你出来的
Dude, I had to ask you out.
抱歉我让你久等了 你听过“彬彬有礼”这个词吗？
Well, excuse me for waiting.
听好了 这是关于让你得到应得的东西
You ever hear of chivalry? Listen, this is about you getting what you deserve.
我在学校非常努力 因为我觉得 如果我们俩
I'm killing myself at school because I think it's gonna be worth it for both of us.
搬到一起住的话 这些努力会是值得的
You know, if we move in together.
等等 什么？等等 嘿 你刚才说了什么？
Wait, what? What? W-W-Wait. Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey. What was that?
你刚才说了什么？
What'd you just say?
我是说我们不能 继续在你爸家铺水管
Well, I mean, we can't keep, you know, laying pipe
尽量不发出声音 盯着那张愚蠢的比利乔尔的海…
at your dad's place. Trying to be all quiet. Staring up at that dumb Billy Joel post. . .
海报
-. . . poster. Hey.
嘿 你绝不可以
Don't you ever besmirch Billy Jo. . .
诋毁比利乔尔
我停不下来
I can't stop. I can't stop. I can't stop. I can't stop.
Can't stop. Can't stop.
洛缤？
Robin?
洛缤！
Robin!
: Robin!
爱荷华州 得梅因
♪ You lying so low into the weeds ♪
♪ I bet you gonna ambush me ♪
♪ You'd have me down, down, down ♪
♪ Down on my knees. . . ♪
让能量穿透这堵墙
Let the energy go through the wall.
我是星光 50公斤不到 1米68
I am Starlight. I'm 110 pounds, and I'm five foot six.
请转过来
CASTING DIRECTOR: Turn around, please.
好的 给我们看看 亲爱的
Okay. Let's see it, dear.
你应该把头转过去
-You should look away. Sorry?
你说什么？
你不要看摄像机 而且要闭上眼睛
You should turn away from the camera,
否则我会把你弄瞎的
and you should close your eyes, or else I'll blind you.
好的
All right.
好了 开始吧
Okay, go ahead.
非常抱歉 你还好吗？
I am so sorry. Are you all right?
我出生的时候就有超能力
I was born Super-Abled.
我妈妈高兴坏了
Uh, my mom was thrilled.
她带我去参加 所有小英雄小姐选美
She took me to all the little miss hero pageants,
但我很不喜欢
but I hated it.
我还能闻到喷发定型剂的气味
Ugh, I mean, I can still. . . smell the hairspray.
但是
Uh, but. . .
在问答环节 他们总是问我我的愿望是什么
. . . at the Q and A, they always asked me what my wish was,
我总是说：“拯救世界”
and I always said, "to save the world. "
评委总会咯咯笑 好像觉得我的答案很可爱
And the judges just chuckled
like it was cute.
但那对我来说并不是个玩笑
But it wasn't a joke to me.
从什么时候开始 怀抱希望与天真无邪 变成了一码事了？
Since when did "hopeful" and "naive"
become the same thing?
如果不是为了拯救世界 你为什么会进入这一行？
I mean, why would you get into this business
if not to save the world?
这就是我一直想要的
That's all I have ever wanted.
因此 我一直希望能进入超级七人队
And that's why I've always wanted
to be in The Seven.
谢谢 珍妮弗
ANCHOR: Thanks, Jennifer.
我觉得洛缤的葬礼很不错
Thought Robin's service was nice.
你看到有多少人来了吗？
Did you see how many people came? Wow.
大家很尊重她 现场充满了爱意
Lot of respect for that girl. Lot of love in the room.
还有那些餐点 真丰盛
And the spread. What a spread.
真的很不错
Just really nice.
但那都不能传达…
MADELYN: That does not begin to convey
新闻 火车头献上最深切的哀悼
the terrible regret. . .
-…沉痛的慰问… 也许在播放电影之类的…
Aw, geez. Maybe there's a movie on.
不 别换台
-No, keep it. No, we can switch it.
-不 我们可以换台 就看这个
-Keep it. . . . awful, tragic loss.
我向洛缤沃德的家人送上最深切的哀悼
My deepest condolences to Robin Ward's family.
我当时正在追捕银行劫犯
I was chasing these bank robbers.
她刚好走到了马路中间 而我当时不能…
She just stepped in the middle of the street, and I-I couldn't. . .
“中间”…她当时离该死的路牙 还有半步距离
Middle of the. . . She was a half step off the fucking curb.
冷静 别这样 休伊 别生气 好吗？
Oh, now, come on, Hughie. Just, uh, don't get upset, okay? Just. . .
就…他心知肚明
He knows. MADELYN: . . . swift, thoughtful attention. . .
Now I think that A-Train would like to get back to work.
在沃特的每个人 都为洛缤感到很难过
MAN: Everyone at Vought is just. . . just wrecked about Robin.
你们俩并没有结婚
Now, you two weren't married, and look,
严格来说 并没有合法索赔
technically, there's no legal claim.
但沃特想做该做的事
But. . . Vought wants to do the right thing:
赔偿你4万5千美元
offer you $45, 000 in restitution.
你只需要在这里签名 我就可以给你支票
All you have to do is sign right here,
and I'll offer you the check.
这是一个保密协议
This is a confidentiality agreement.
就是个常见的保密协议
It's a boilerplate NDA.
签了这个我就不能再谈这件事？
I sign this, and. . .
I can't talk about it?
我要假装这事没有发生过？
Have to pretend like it didn't happen,
就好像我当时手里没有抓着洛缤的手臂？
like I wasn't holding Robin's arms in my hands?
我知道你很难过 但我们只是想帮你
Look, I know you're upset, but we're just trying to help.
那就说“对不起”
Then say you're sorry.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
你们的人说：“我们的哀悼” “我们的慰问”以及“我们很遗憾”
I mean, you people say "our condolences"
and "my sympathies" and "our regrets, "
但没有一个人看着我的眼睛说 “对不起！”
but nobody can look me in the fucking eye and say "I'm sorry. "
我什么都不签 出去
I'm not signing anything. Get out.
我说了 滚出去！
I said get the hell out!
你还好吗？
You okay?
正如我所说 这是个常见的保密协议 真的挺普通的
As I said, boilerplate NDA, really.
Pretty standard stuff.
我可以考虑一下吗？
Can I think about it?
如果你有任何疑问 就…
If you have any questions at all, just, uh. . .
44号警员 交通事故 地址是第63号大街1420号…
DISPATCHER: Unit 44, code 20. Address is 1420 63rd Street. . .
外面有疯子在闹事吗？
Any maniacs out there?
安静的夜晚
Mm-mm. Quiet night. Like every night.
每个夜晚都一样
That's too bad.
太糟了 我们现在真的需要媒体曝光率
We could really use the press right now.
安妮
Oh, Annie.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
别担心 我没有得到那份工作
Don't worry. I didn't get the job.
这可难说
You don't know that.
他们在全国找女孩面试
They're auditioning girls nationwide.
再说 可能是伯爵夫人得到了那份工作 她在演播室的表现很好
Besides, Countess probably got it. She's so good in a room.
如果你态度消极 就会遇到不好的事
If you're negative, negative things happen to you.
喂？是的 我是她妈妈
Hello? Yes, I'm her mother.
好的 等一下
Uh, yes. Uh. . . uh, one moment.
是他们打来的
: It's them. It's them.
喂？是的 我就是
Hello? Yes, this is she.
我被选上了？
I got it?
你被选上了！
-You got it! You got it!
Shh.
我的天啊
: Oh, my God.
真抱歉 刚才信号不好
Uh, I'm so. . . I'm so sorry. It's a weird connection.
我其实不知道刚才是怎么回事
I don't know what that was, actually. Uh. . . Mm-hmm.
她身上没有身份证 但是有件事
HUGHIE: Oh, shit.
是吗？
MAN: Yeah?
我认为她是个瘾君子
MAN 2: I think she was an addict.
针孔？
MAN: Needle tracks?
在一只手臂上坑坑洼洼的
MAN 2: 12 marks on one arm.
更多的毒品正在进来
MAN: More dope coming in.
更多的毒贩工作
More pushers at work.
-你在干什么？ 人渣
What you doing?
不能以刑事案件起诉火车头
Can't file a criminal case
超人类就像警察一样 他们执行任务时造成伤亡的话不受指控
against A-Train. Supes are like cops. They can't be charged
好吧
-for damages while they're on the job. Okay.
但也许我们可以以“疏忽致死”的罪名起诉他
But maybe we can file a wrongful death.
我得让洛缤的父母同意这事
I just got to get Robin's parents to sign off on it.
休伊 过来跟我坐坐
-Hughie, come sit with me. Dad, I'm not. . .
爸爸 我正在…
-I'm right. . .
好吧
Okay.
你真好样的
Good for you.
你要为洛缤伸张正义
You want to make this right, what happened to Robin.
但你不能
But you can't.
所以签了这个吧
So sign this.
什么？
What?
这是很大一笔钱 休伊 我们真的能用得上这笔钱
This is a lot of money, Hughie.
We could really use it.
我不能…爸爸 他们杀死了她
I can't Dad, they killed her.
现实一点 好吗？就算我们付得起律师费 我们很可能付不起
Be realistic, okay? Even if we could pay for a lawyer--
案件也不成立
and that's a big if there's no case.
她当时在街道上 就当她是被公共汽车撞了
She was in the street. Be like if a bus hit her. Dad, she was one step
爸爸 她当时离路牙有一步之遥！ 我亲眼所见！
-off the curb. I. . .
-I saw it! Hughie, look. Look.
这事你做不成的
-You can't do this. Why not?
-为什么不能？爸爸 我有… 你没有斗志 你从来就没有
-Dad, I have. . . You don't have the fight.
You never have.
对不起 但这是真的
I'm sorry, but it's-it's true.
我也没有
Neither do I.
好了 过来跟我坐一坐 好吗？
Now. . . come and. . . come and sit with me, okay?
在播《雷明顿斯蒂尔》呢
Remington Steele's on.
休伊？你要去哪里？
-Hughie! Where you going?
…在沃特总部外面 在这里开年度股东…
TV REPORTER: . . . the red carpet outside of Vought headquarters, here for the annual shareholders presentation. . .
她到了 欢迎来到纽约
ASHLEY: There she is. Welcome to New York.
我是艾诗丽巴瑞特 人才及关系部主管
I'm Ashley Barrett, director of talent relations.
那这些人全都是为了我来这里的吗？
So, uh, are all these people here for me?
亲爱的 他们还能是为了谁来这里的？
Oh, honey. Who else would they be here for?
来吧 我们迟到了
Come on. We're running late.
天啊
Oh, my God.
星光！
女士们、先生们 毫无疑问
MADELYN: Ladies and gentlemen,
现在是加入超级英雄行业的好时机
it is without a doubt a good time to be in the Superhero business.
我们的净收入提高了14%
Our net income is up 14%.
我们最新的一部电影《G人：世界大战》
Our latest film, G-Men: World War,
在全球收入票房几乎有17亿美元
just grossed shy of $1. 7 billion world-wide.
今年秋天 我们在巴黎外的最新主题公园动土
And this fall, we break ground on our newest theme park outside of Paris.
品牌机会无穷无尽
The branding opportunities are limitless.
但大家知道 这一切都不是真正重要的
But, you know, none of that really matters.
因为最重要的工作是管理、支持
Because job one is managing, supporting,
及建议勇敢的英雄们
and advising the brave heroes
他们每天为了我们
who put themselves in harm's way each and every day
阻止伤害发生
for us.
我们来看一看
Let's take a look.
沃特国际2019年度股东大会
没有犯罪的世界 所有人享受自由与正义
♪ ♪ MADELYN : A world without crime,
with liberty and justice for all,
多亏了沃特家族的
that's within our reach,
两百多名超级英雄 这个理想离我们并不远
thanks to the 200-plus Superheroes
我们看到在光明的未来 每一个小镇…
in the Vought Family. We see a bright future ahead,
都有一个沃特英雄
where there is a Vought Hero in every town.
对了 你迄今表现非常好
You're doing really well, by the way, so far.
我什么都没有做
I-I haven't done anything yet.
正是如此 你在18至49岁的 中西部及保守天主教徒中的
Yeah, exactly. You're already up
支持率已经领先了百分之二点五
two-and-a-half points with Midwesterners and conservative Christians in 18 to 49.
顺便提一下 你面试的那段讲话
That speech, by the way, your audition--
很谦逊、谦虚 非常聪明的选择
It was modest; it was humble. Really fucking smart choice.
我当时是认真的
Uh, I-I meant it.
是的 所以我们才爱你
ASHLEY: Yeah, that's why we love you.
你准备好了改变自己的生活吗？
So you ready for your life to change?
火车头
MADELYN : . . . including the jewel
包括沃特皇冠上的珍宝
in Vought's crown,
深海 透明人
the greatest superhero team
玄色
梅芙女王 祖国人
the world's ever seen:
世上迄今最强大的超级英雄 超级七人队
The Seven.
这是我们的职责、荣誉 我们是沃特 我们成就超级英雄
That is our job, our honor.
We are Vought.
沃特国际
We make heroes super.
我有一个非常棒的惊喜给大家
I have a very exciting surprise for you.
超级七人队的成员及七大洋之主
Both a member of The Seven,
and Lord of the Seven Seas,
亲自到场 有请深海！
live and in person, the Deep.
♪ ♪
谢谢
DEEP: Thank you.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everybody.
在超级七人队
After a long,
服务了很久并取得卓越成就后
distinguished career with The Seven,
我的好朋友点灯人退休了
my good friend, the Lamplighter, has retired.
我们向他致谢 你们觉得如何？
Let's give him a big "thank you. " What do you say?
AUDIENCE MEMBER: Thank you, Lamplighter!
但现在 随着我们转向未来
But now,
as we turn towards the future,
我想介绍一位很特别的人
I'd like to introduce someone very special.
我迫不及待想跟她合作
And I, for one, can't wait to work with her.
请欢迎星光
Please welcome Starlight.
去吧 叫你呢
Go. Go. That's you.
女士们、先生位 星光和深海！
-Ooh, look at that. MADELYN: Ladies and gentlemen, Starlight and the Deep.
-♪ ♪
我爱你 星光
Oh. Hi. MAN : I love you, Starlight! ♪ ♪
我们爱你们！
WOMAN : We love you!
加速子弹啤酒
火车头麦片 很不错！
嘿 伙计 你没事吧？
: Hey, buddy, you okay?
嘿 伙计！
Hey, buddy!
Wow.
很厉害 对吧？
Pretty cool, huh?
看看这个 我们在环地球轨道上
Oh, hey, check this out. We have two World View-4 satellites
有两个世界观4号卫星
in geocentric orbit.
基本上能从600多公里的高空 读取逃逸车辆的车牌号
We can essentially read a getaway car's license plate from 380 miles up.
这真是…
That is just. . .
我是说…
I mean. . .
天啊 我以前用的 是从易趣网上买来的一个警讯监控仪
G I was working with a police scanner
是的 你现在不再用那个了
that I bought on eBay. Yeah, well, not anymore you're not.
等你看到了餐厅再说吧
Oh, and wait till you check out the dining room.
我们也许从格莱莫西酒馆偷了米罗 也许没有
We, uh, may or may not have stolen Miro
from Gramercy Tavern.
是的 他真的非常棒
Yeah, he's fan-fucking-tastic.
那是他的 对吗？
That's his, isn't it?
祖国人的？是的
Homelander's? Yeah.
但你很快就会有自己的座位了
But you'll have your own soon.
来 过来 试一下
Here. Come on. Give it a test drive.
来吧
Come on.
你还好吧？
O-Oh, you-you okay?
只是…
It's just. . .
我以前常站在镜子前面
I used to stand in the mirror,
假装自己在我现在身处的地方
pretending to be where I am right now.
你知道吗？我第一天工作的时候
You know something? On my first day, I, uh. . .
感觉…自己像是个骗子
Well, I-I felt like a fraud.
是的 好消息是大家都有同感
Yeah. But the good news is, everybody feels that way.
谢谢
Thank you.
但是我们现在是一队的 我们会相互帮助
And, hey, we're a team now. We'll help each other out.
我打赌你从小就在墙上 贴了一张祖国人的海报
I bet growing up you had a poster of Homelander on your wall, huh?
不 其实 我…
No, actually, I. . .
我也说不清 祖国人是那么…
I don't know, Homelander's so--
他就像是耶稣之类的
He's like Jesus or something.
如果你想听实话
If you want to know the truth,
我其实贴了一张你的海报
I actually had a poster of you.
什么？真的？
Really?
是的 我有点…
-Yeah. Yeah. I kind of Oh.
我对你有种女学生的迷恋
I kind of had a schoolgirl crush on you.
-我的… 我的天啊
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我希望说出来不会太唐突
I hope that's not inappropriate to say.
不 一点都不会唐突
No, no, no, no, no. It's not inappropriate at all.
就是有点疯狂
-It's just, it's kind of wild.
怎么了？
What?
你刚才说了迷恋我 我想着 你知道…
I mean, you said you had a crush on me. I figured that, you know. . .
嘿 听着 你很美
-That is. . . Whoa, whoa, wh-wh-whoa, hey. Look, you're gorgeous.
我不是指做爱
I'm not I'm not talking about sex,
就是来点口交
just a little bit of pole-smoking.
嘿 等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
这只关乎你到底有多渴望进入超级七人队
It's just a question of how bad you want to be in The Seven.
你说什么？
-Excuse me? Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
别激动
Hey, hey, hey. Hey. Take it easy.
冷静 我们只是在聊天而已
Settle down. We're just, we're just talking.
听着 我知道你很强大 我明白
And look, I know that you're powerful.
你的超能力可不是盖的
I get it. Your powers are no joke.
问题是 我是这里的二把手
The thing is. . . I am number two around here.
所以要是我发话 你就会被赶出这里
So, like, if I say so, you know, you'd be out of here.
尤其是在你袭击我之后
Especially since you attacked me.
我什么？
I what?
是的 你看
Yeah. Look.
爱荷华州的甜心 得梅因的守护者
I mean, Iowa's sweetheart, the Defender of Des Moines,
精神错乱 疯狂袭击了深海
just went psycho on the Deep.
我是说 那能让你从这一行消失的
I mean, that. . . that could put you out of the business.
是的
Yeah.
尾巴夹在两腿之间 回家去找妈妈
I mean, home to Mommy, tail tucked between your legs.
想想所有那些孩子们 我是指那些孩子们
Just think of all those kids. I mean, the kids.
所有那些崇拜你的孩子 他们会悲痛欲绝的
Those kids who look up to you, they'd just be shattered.
那并不是你真正想要的 对吗？
I mean, th-that's not what you really want, right?
或者我们可以组成团队
Or we come together as a team.
你和我一起随机应变
You and me, we just roll with the punches,
也许只需要三分钟
for, like, three minutes, maybe.
这没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
然后 你知道会发生什么吗？
And then you know what happens?
你所有的梦想都会实现
All your dreams come true.
我肯定你们全都听说了
I-I'm sure you guys have all heard
透明人昨天晚上在扬克斯 阻止了一起入室行窃案
that Translucent stopped a home invasion
一个年轻的单亲妈妈和她的两个小孩 真是不可思议 真的…
in Yonkers last night, a young, single mother and her two kids.
Just incredible. Just. . .
告诉我们 你怎么能够消失？
So tell us, how are you able to-to vanish?
不 我并不是真正消失
No, I don't actually vanish.
我的皮肤变成一种碳素超颖材料
My skin turns into this carbon meta-material
可以像隐身斗篷一样
that bends the light.
让光线弯曲
Like an invisibility cloak.
好的 我们要问清楚 你必须全裸 对吗？
All right, but just to be clear, you have to be completely naked, right?
很感激你来上节目 老兄 我很爱你们
I appreciate you coming on the show, my man. I love you.
请继续收看《隐形力量2》的幕后花絮
You guys stay tuned for a behind-the-scenes look
稍后 透明人本人…
at Invisible Force 2, and later, Translucent himself. . .
你对保姆监控摄像头感兴趣？
You interested in a nanny cam?
因为我们正好在搞特价
'Cause we're actually running a special on that.
这只熊挺受欢迎的 眼睛里有摄像头
Um, it's a pretty popular bear. There's cameras in the eyes.
告诉我 有多少保姆会摇晃宝宝？
BUTCHER: Tell me, how many nannies shake their babies?
你说什么？
Uh, I'm sorry?
就是猛烈地摇晃 就像…
You know, a good. . . hard shake, like. . .
想把番茄酱从瓶子里挤出来一样
like tryin' to get ketchup out of a bottle.
1%？更少？
One percent? Less?
我并不知道
I-I don't really know.
真好笑
Funny, that.
他们这种破产品 在全世界有10亿美元的销售额
They sell a billion dollars worth of that shit worldwide.
挺能说明问题的 不是吗？
Goes to show you, doesn't it?
如果你能把人吓唬住
The bollocks people will believe
他们愿意相信一些胡说八道
if you get them scared enough. Cool.
好
Cool, cool.
很好
Um. . .
今天有什么需要我帮忙的吗 还是…
Is there anything I can help you with today, or. . . ?
我不给你添乱了 休伊
I'm not gonna piss you about, Hughie.
我听说洛缤的事了
I heard what happened to Robin.
不好意思 你是谁？
I'm-I'm-I'm sorry, who are you?
她当时并不是在街道上 她离那个路牙有一步之遥
She wasn't in the street. She was one step off the fucking curb.
而你没有接受赔偿
And you didn't take the pay-off.
是的 我问你呢 你到底是谁？ 你怎么知道这些的？
Yeah. I said, who the hell are you?
我叫布彻尔
How do you know that? Name's Butcher.
比利布彻尔
Billy Butcher.
联调局
听着 我想着你和我应该聊一聊
Listen, I was thinking that, uh, you and me should have a little bit of a chat.
你是联邦调查员？
Y-You're a Fed? You don't sound like a Fed.
-你听起来不像联邦调查员 怎么了？我不能是移民？
What, I can't immigrate?
海港那里有座巨大的绿色雕像
There's a giant green slapper with her ass in the harbor
它所象征的可不是这样
that says different.
你看起来也不像
You don't really look like one, either.
不像？那我看起来像什么？
No? What do I look like?
像是你是色情版《黑客帝国》的主演
Like you're starring in a porn version of The Matrix.
上面白纸黑字写着呢
Well, it's all right there in black and white.
好吧 我到底能为你做什么？
Okay. Uh, what exactly can I do for you?
不 你完全理解错了 休伊
No, you got it all wrong, Hughie.
应该是我能为你做什么
It's what I can do for you.
明白吗 你并不是一个人 小子
You see, you ain't alone, son.
这种事比你以为的要多很多
It happens a lot more than you think.
超人类每年间接害死几百人
Supes lose hundreds of people each year to collateral damage.
不 少来了 那样的话新闻早就大肆报道了 大家会尖叫着说那是该死的谋杀
No. Come on, that'd be all over the news. People would be screaming bloody murder.
是的 时不时也许会有些不合时宜的报道
Yeah, look, there might be the odd mention
例如关于洛缤的新闻
of it now and again, like with Robin,
但是更多所发生的事被隐瞒了
but there's a fuck-sight more that happens that just gets swept right under the rug.
为什么？
Why?
这不是很明显吗？
Ain't it obvious?
大洋地 潜入深海
Movie tickets, merchandising,
电影票、文化衍生品、主题公园、电子游戏
theme parks, video games.
价值几十亿的全球工业
A multi-billion dollar global industry supported
受企业说客
by corporate lobbyists
及两党政客的支持
and politicians on both sides.
但你不会听到这些报道的主要原因
But the main reason that you won't hear about it
是因为公众不想知道
is 'cause the public don't want to know about it.
人们喜欢超人类带给他们的那种舒适感
See, people love that cozy feeling that Supes give them.
有些美好的王八蛋会从天而降 拯救世界
Some golden cunt to swoop out of the sky and save the day
好让他们不必亲自去做这件事
so you don't got to do it yourself.
但如果知道他们一半的勾当…
But if you knew half the shit they get up to. . .
Ooh. . .
十恶不赦
Fuckin' diabolical.
但这正是我发挥作用之处
But then. . . that's where I come in.
发挥什么作用？
Come in to. . . to do what?
混蛋越界时惩罚他们
Spank the bastards when they get out of line.
你怎样惩罚超人类？
How do you spank a Supe?
来吧 小子
Come on, son. Uh, where?
去哪里？
你会很喜欢的
You'll love it.
不可能
Uh, not likely. Uh, listen.
听着 我认为这够了 我不去了
I think this is good; I'm good.
谢谢你这番非常奇怪的谈话
Uh, thank you for an extremely weird conversation,
但我不想跟你去第二个地方
but, uh, I don't want to go to a second location with you.
我要回去工作了
So, I'm gonna get back to work.
谢谢
Thank you.
休伊
Hughie! Hughie.
这是你唯一的机会
This is your one and only, mate.
我一旦离开 你就见不到我了
Once I go, I'm gone.
我正在给你一个机会 惩罚害死你女朋友的人
I'm offering you the opportunity
to get them that got your girl.
你会能失去什么
What have you got to lose
你还没有失去的东西？
that you ain't already lost?
♪ ♪
我们在哪里？
Where are we?
闭上你的嘴巴
Keep your mouth shut.
哈利 收到你的信息了
Harry. Got your message.
谢谢你这位正直的市民
Thank you for being an upstanding citizen.
你知道这是该死的警察暴行
You know this is fucking police brutality, man.
我给你开门被他们抓到 你知道他们会怎样对待我吗？
You know what they'll do to me, they catch me letting you in?
不及我对你折磨的一半 如果你不开门的话
Not half of what I'll do if you don't.
你刚才说你是警察？
Did he just say you were police?
是的 警察 联调员 在这种地方全都一样
Yeah, you know, cop, Fed, all the same to twats like that.
♪ ♪
我的天啊
Holy shit.
别目瞪口呆的 要试着混入人群
Pick your jaw up off the floor and try to blend in.
这是超人类能够满足他们肮脏的小癖好
This is the only place where the Supes can scratch their filthy little itch
而不是会狗仔队拍照的唯一地方
without the paps taking snaps. ♪ I did a bad, bad thing ♪
♪ I did a bad, bad thing ♪
那是伊兹奇尔
Wait, wait, wait. That's Ezekiel. ♪ I did a bad, bad thing. ♪
基督的披风那个家伙
The "Capes for Christ" guy. . .
宣扬“祈祷所有同性恋消失”的那个
preaches all that. . . "pray the gay away" shit.
现在他正左拥右抱两个男人呢
BUTCHER: And now he's the meat in the Manwich.
该死的伪君子
Fucking hypocrite.
♪ You ever pray with all your heart and soul ♪
♪ Just to watch her walk away? Yeah. . . ♪
继续播放
BUTCHER: Keep going forward.
对了 继续
That's it. Further.
继续
Further.
就是那里
There. There.
停
-Stop. HUGHIE: Wait, wait, wait.
等等 火车头现在就在这里？
A-Train's. . . A-Train's here right now?
曾经 这是昨天晚上拍的 打开声音
Was. This is from last night. Turn it up.
真不敢相信你把一个贱人撞成了肉酱
I cannot believe you ran through a bitch.
你想听件很疯狂的事吗？
A-TRAIN: You want to hear something crazy?
我撞穿她的身体时跑得太快 吞下了她一颗臼齿
I ran so fast through this bitch that I swallowed one of her molars.
就好像是高速公路上的一只虫子
Like a bug on the fucking freeway.
老兄 真恶心
Dude, that's nasty.
他们在笑
They're laughing.
就好像她是个笑话一样
Just. . . Like she's a joke.
他妈的居然在笑
They're fucking laughing.
那你打算怎么做？
So what are you gonna do about it?
沃特
老天爷 把你自己弄干净
Oh, for Chrissakes. Clean yourself up.
绝不能让他们看到你这个样子
Never let them see you like this.
透明人 你是个该死的变态
Translucent, you're a goddamn pervert.
Ah. . .
Oh, uh. . .
我还是走吧
I'll just go.
他们都是那样的人？
HUGHIE: They're all like that?
全都是？连祖国人也是？
All of them? Even Homelander?
祖国人是个例外
Homelander's the exception.
他不喝酒 不抽烟
He doesn't drink, doesn't smoke.
那家伙是个圣人
Man's a saint.
其他人都是的 让那些混蛋去死吧 我这么说请见谅
But the rest of 'em, yeah. Pardon my French, fuck those fuckers.
来 看看这个
Here. Have a shufti of that.
这是什么？
-What are these? That's the police log
洛缤遇害当天的警察日志
the day that Robin got murdered.
几场酒吧斗殴 几辆车被盗
Couple of bar fights. A few cars got nicked.
但你知道里面没有记录什么吗？
But you know what's not in there?
没有银行警报响起
No bank alarms going off.
警局拘押室没有人被起诉
No one charged at Central Booking.
火车头才没有阻止两个银行抢劫犯 有人肯定是隐瞒了什么
A-Train stopped two bank robbers, my arse. Someone's fucking hiding something.
-隐瞒了什么？ 不知道
-Hiding what? Well, I don't know,
就是他那天晚上逃避的事
whatever dodgy shit he was up to that night.
他为什么停不下来？那个袋子里的是什么？
Why couldn't he stop? I mean, what was in that bag?
他在躲着谁？
You know? Who was he running from?
-还是说他要跑去哪里？ 说对了
-Or where was he running to? Bingo.
查清楚这事 我们就能抓住这个混蛋
Work that out, and we'll have the fucker, I can smell it.
我有预感
Okay.
好的
好的 那…
Okay, so, um. . .
我帮上什么忙？
what can I do to help? Here's what you do.
下面就是你要做的事
打电话给沃特 告诉他们你会拿那笔钱 签保密协议
Ring Vought, tell 'em you'll take the money, sign the NDA,
但要求签协议时 火车头亲自到场
but only if A-Train's there in person when you do it.
为什么需要火车头亲自到场？
Why does A-Train need to be there?
然后他们会带你过超级七人塔的安检
Then they'll take you into The Seven Tower,
-然后你要装一个窃听器 窃听器？
through security, mate, and then you're gonna plant a bug. A bug?
窃听器 能让我们窃听他们
A bug. And we'll have a little listen.
了解他们到底在搞什么鬼
See what's really going on.
好 抱歉 我先问清楚
Okay, let me just. . . sorry, let me just get this straight.
你要我一个人去超级七人塔
You want me to. . . you want me to go to Seven Tower by myself,
而且你要我装一个窃听器？
and-and you want me to plant a bug,
怎么？就好像 我是该死的詹姆斯邦德一样？
like I'm. . . what, like I'm fuckin' James Bond?
是的 正是如此 你听懂了
-Yeah, exactly. You got it. You're FBI.
你是联调局的
你是联调局的 那就弄个搜查令啊 你为什么需要我？
If you're FBI, then get a warrant. Why do you. . . why do you even need me? Hughie, Hughie,
休伊 听好了 伙计
look, mate, I got a warrant, all right?
我有搜查令 好吗？
但那个地方受保护
But that place is firewalled, untappable,
没办法窃听 而且封锁严密 比尼姑的裤头还紧
and locked up tighter than a nun's knickers.
我一辈子都不可能亲自进去里面
I couldn't get myself in there in a million years.
但你 小子 你可以进去
But you, son, you could do it.
-不 我不能 好吗？ 可以的
-No, no, I can't, okay? Yeah.
我不能 不 你是没有看到火车头浑身…
I can't. No. You didn't see A-Train covered in. . .
然后怎么样？我进去那里
And-and I'm, what, I'm just supposed to go in there,
然后要跟他握手并微笑？
and I'm supposed to. . . I'm supposed to shake his hand?
-And smile? Yeah.
我不…你知道我最爱的音乐家是谁吗？
I'm not. . . Do you know who my favorite musician is?
-是谁？ 詹姆斯泰勒
-Who? James Taylor.
然后是西蒙和加芬克尔 再然后是比利乔尔
Number two, Simon & Garfunkel. Number three, Billy Joel.
他们没有一个能渗透到众人当中 好吗？
Any of those guys, they don't infiltrate.
我不是一个潜入者
Okay? I'm not an infiltrator.
休伊 拿出点勇气来 你刚才听到了那个混蛋笑你女朋友
Hughie, Hughie, fucking grow a pair. You heard that cunt laughing at your girl.
不 我不能
No. No. No. No, I can't. I can't do that.
我做不来
I'm sorry, I'm just gonna fuck it up,
对不起 我肯定会把这事搞砸的
装不了你的窃听器
and you're not gonna have your bug. . .
而且我会没命的
: . . . and I'll be dead.
我跟你不一样
I'm not. . . I'm not like you.
送给梅森 触摸天空！ 祝好 祖国人
: This is amazing, Madelyn.
太棒了 玛德琳 谢谢你送我这个
Thank you for this. My kid is gonna lose his mind.
我的孩子肯定会高兴得疯掉的
我们很荣幸 别在网上出售就好
Ah, it is our pleasure. Just do not sell it online.
好了 你有什么想法？
All right. What are you thinking?
巴尔的摩是个美丽的城市
Baltimore is a beautiful town.
但你们有个问题
But you've got a problem.
你们的谋杀案件增加了多少？62%？
Your homicide rates are up, what, 62%?
警察无法破案
The police are not closing cases.
你们都快需要联邦生命线资助了
You're on the verge of needing a federal lifeline.
有话直说 玛德琳
Cut to the chase, Madelyn.
你有什么提议？
Who are you proposing?
努比亚王子 他适合你们的人口组成
Nubian Prince. Fits your population's demo,
但不会太好战
but not too militant.
白种人也喜欢他 赞成率59%
Caucasians love him, too, with a. . . 59% approval rate.
我愿意给你一份三年的独家合约
I am willing to give you a three-year exclusive contract
附送全面的公关支持
with full PR support,
而且我给你衍生文化品销售的
and I'm gonna give you nine and a half points
百分之九点五
of the merchandising.
我以为他在底特律
I thought he was in Detroit.
我们正考虑采取行动
Well, we're thinking about making a move.
多少钱？
How much?
一年3亿
-$300 million a year.
我知道 金额巨大
I know, I know, it's a tough swallow.
但我们俩都知道你的城市需要一个英雄
But we both know that your city needs a hero.
2亿买努比亚王子 我可以说服民众
$200 million for Nubian Prince.
-I can sell that. Mm.
抱歉 史蒂夫 我不能接受
I'm sorry, Steve, I can't do it.
亚特兰大正排队等着呢
We've got Atlanta waiting in the wings.
我想也许你可以
-I think maybe you can.
为什么？
And why is that?
我恰好知道“五号化合物”的事
I happen to know about Compound V.
“五号化合物”是什么？
What is Compound V?
就是能真正
It's the type of rumor
败坏你那些英雄的声名的谣言
that could really tarnish those heroes of yours.
没有人想看到这种情况 人们需要英雄
Nobody wants that. People need heroes.
我可以确保那只会是谣言
Now, I can make sure that that stays a rumor,
因为我是你们的朋友
because I'm a friend.
但友谊有利也有弊
But friendship does cut both ways.
抱歉 史蒂夫 我不知道你在说些什么
I'm sorry, Steve, I don't know what you're talking about.
价格就是3亿
$300 million is the price,
否则我们就去亚特兰大
or we go to Atlanta.
星光 她就像我们一样！
DONNA: So, how amazing is it?
那里面到底有多棒？祖国人是怎么样的人？
What's Homelander like?
他很忙 我还没见到他呢 但是…
Uh. . . he's busy. I haven't really met him yet, but. . .
妈妈 我必须告诉你发生了什么事
Mom, I got to tell you what happened.
我忘了
Oh, I forgot.
我有一次跟帕蒂和翠诗打麻将
I was playing mah-jongg with Patty and Trish,
帕蒂一直不停地说
and Patty is going on and on about how her daughter
她女儿进了医学院
got into med school, and I'm thinking, so what?
我就心想：“那又怎么样？”
我女儿进了超级七人队
My daughter got into The Seven!
好了 你刚才想跟我说什么？
Anyway, so-so, what did you want to tell me?
一切都很好
Everything's great.
就像我们梦想的一样
Just how we dreamed. Um. . .
妈妈 你知道吗？我得挂了
Mom, actually, you know what? I have to go.
好的 拜 宝贝
All right. Bye, honey.
Um. . .
打扰了 不好意思 你还好吗？
excuse me. I'm sorry, a-are you okay?
刚才那通电话似乎让人难过
Just seemed like a. . . tough call.
-抱歉 我不是故意烦你的 不会 没事
Sorry. I don't mean to bother you. No, no, it's okay.
我很好 只是…
Uh. . . I'm fine. I'm just. . .
我只是今天过得不太好
I'm just having a bad day.
我也是
: Yeah, me, too.
是工作上的事 还是
Uh. . . is it, like, a-a work thing, or. . .
生活上的事？
a-a life thing?
工作上的事
It's a work thing.
你呢？
You? Uh. . . life thing.
生活上的事
你知道一个人会对自己有某种认识
You know how you have this. . .
image of yourself?
比如说 我以前以为自己很坚强
Like, I thought I was strong.
你明白吗？
You know? Like, made of steel.
钢筋铁骨 是一个斗士
A fighter.
然后我遇到了一个混蛋 遇到了一个
And. . . then I was faced with this horrible situation
很可怕的情况
with this asshole. . .
然后…
and. . .
我在脑海里听见我妈妈的声音在说
I just heard my mom's voice in my head,
“保持微笑 表演必须继续”
"Keep smiling, the show must go on, "
我并没有抗争
and. . . I didn't fight.
现在我觉得很恶心
And now I just feel sick.
部分原因是因为我做了那种事 但…
Partly because I did it, but. . .
主要是因为…
mostly because. . .
原来我并不是自己所想的那种人
. . . turns out I'm not who I thought I was.
很抱歉 我不是故意要把这些事告诉你
-Oh. Oh, I'm, um, sorry. Uh. . . I-I didn't mean to just dump all of that
-给你造成负担的 不 你说出来完全关系
-onto you. No, no, it's totally fine that you dumped. Um. . .
你喜欢你的工作吗？
Listen, d-do you like your job?
那是我唯一想要的东西
Oh. It's the only thing I've ever wanted.
那它是份好工作
And it's a good job?
你不是在向孩子贩毒吧？
Like, you're not selling kids smack?
不是 那是份很好的工作
No, it's a great job.
我可以帮助许多人
I could help a lot of people.
是这样的 我…
Thing is, I, um. . .
以前认识一个女孩
used to know this girl,
我们以前常去洛克菲勒中心滑冰
and we used to go skating at Rockefeller,
我会在旁边 死死地抓着扶手
and I'd be on the side with this death grip on the rails.
她则会一头冲进溜冰场中间
She would just charge headfirst into the middle of the rink.
而且她并不是…
And she wasn't. . . good.
很厉害
她经常…
Like, she fell--
摔倒
a lot--
但她从来都不怕
but she was never scared.
她以前总是说
And she always used to say:
“你摔倒了并不意味着你必须原地不动”
"Just 'cause you fall on your ass doesn't mean you have to stay there. "
所以你只是摔倒了 你知道吗？
So you fell on your ass, you know?
那并不是真正的你
That's not who you are.
那真正的你是谁？
So who are you?
我是个斗士
I'm a fighter.
我要战斗
I'm gonna fight.
是的
Yeah.
我要把那个混蛋的脑袋 从他身上
I'm gonna take that son of a bitch's head
直接拔下来
-clean off his body. Okay. Wow, that was. . .
好的 这真是…
好吧
Okay.
不错
-Cool.
有点吓人 但是不错
Little scary, but. . . but-but cool.
对了 我叫休伊
I'm-I'm Hughie, by the way.
我叫安妮
Annie.
♪ ♪
好吧 老兄 我加入
Okay, man. I'm in.
好 正在拨通
Okay, it's ringing.
-喂 你好
DOUG: Yeah, hello? Hi. Hi.
你好
Yes, hello. Hello, Mr. Friedman.
你好 弗里德曼先生 我是休伊坎贝尔
It's Hughie Campbell. I got your message,
我收到了你的信息和4万5千美元 真是…
and-and $45K, it's just. . .
真是…太好了 改变了我的人生
it's just. . . it's bingo, like, life-changing.
但是我签协议前有一个要求 我需要听到道歉
Um, but I just need one thing before I-I sign anything.
-火车头的道歉 他已经道过歉了
I need an apology from A-Train. Uh, he already apologized.
没有
Well, no, no, no.
他并没有 是的 他在电视上
No, he hasn't. Yes, he sent his. . . he sent his regrets and his sympathies on. . .
表达了他的慰问和同情
但如果他可以面对面向我道歉
: on TV, but I-I. . . if I could just get an apology face-to-face,
那就太好了
that would be fantastic.
只是为了结束 为了给这一切画上句号
Just to. . . just for closure, just to put. . . just to put a b-button on it.
好的 是 但是…
Okay, yeah. But, uh. . .
休伊 我告诉你 答案是不行
Hugh, I'm telling you, the answer's gonna be no.
好吧 如果那样的话 你可不可以给…喂？
All right, in that. . . in that case, can you
我觉得…
just give me Uh, hello? I think. . . They hung up.
他们挂断了 我不认为他们会接受
I don't think they're gonna go for it.
会的 他们会的
Hmm. Oh, yes, they will.
星光 你可不想第一次正式会议就迟到
HOMELANDER: Starlight. Don't want to be late to your first official meeting.
我准备好了一篇欢迎致辞
I had a whole welcome speech planned.
抱歉 队长
Sorry, sir.
请 叫我祖国人就好了
Please, Homelander's fine.
我开始寻思你会不会来呢
Beginning to wonder if you'd even show up.
我是说 这么多压力 对任何人而言都很难承受
I mean, all that pressure, it's a lot for anyone to swallow.
是的 别担心 我不会有事的
Yeah. Don't worry, I'll be fine.
我在这里
I'm here, and I'm not going anywhere.
而且我哪儿都不去
我们可以继续开会吗？谢谢
TRANSLUCENT: Can we get back to this, please?
这是很严重的罪案
This is a serious crime. These assholes pirated my movie
这些混蛋在我的电影上映三周前出了盗版
three weeks before release,
走在第五大街上 随便就能看到摆卖
and you can't walk down 5th Avenue without bumping into a table of unlicensed Homelander shirts.
祖国人T恤衫的无牌摊档
侵犯版权每年要损耗沃特12亿元
Copyright infringement is costing Vought $1. 2 billion per year.
那是从我们口袋里掏出去的钱
That's money out of our pockets.
我们有多少 每个人百分之四？
We've all got, what, four points each?
搞什么？
What the fuck?
你们有百分之四？
You got four points?
-还有明显更优秀的律师 嘿 各位 别这样
And clearly better lawyers. Hey, hey, hey, guys, come on.
别吵了
Stop.
听着我们为了一点点钱争吵
What's Starlight gonna think?
星光会怎么看我们？
Listening to us haggling over nickels.
我们可是超级七人队啊 老天爷
We're The Seven, for God's sake.
不管我们是在外面 还是在这里
Whether we're out there or we're in here.
我想听到的是
Now, what I do want to hear
你们这周救什么人
is who you saved this week.
Huh?
谁赞成？
Who's up for that?
玄色
Black Noir.
我们先从你开始
Let's start with you, man.
你养了一只狗？
Do you have a dog?
没有
No.
好了 把你的手机给我们
All right, give us your phone.
要骗过全部安检人员
There's fuck-all security to worry about.
事实上 他们是一群笨蛋
In fact, they're a bunch of muppets.
是的 金属探测器检测不到这个 好吗？
And the metal detector won't pick this up.
他们可能会带你过安检
Right? And what they'll probably do is take you
然后上去会议室
through the security and then up into the boardroom.
坐下来 客气一点 友善一点
Sit down. Be nice, congenial.
然后很礼貌地跟他们说你要去拉一大泡屎
Then, real polite-like, tell 'em you're gonna take a fake shit.
去厕所里 拿出窃听器
Go into the bog, take the bug out.
把塑料撕下来 露出有粘性那一边
Peel back the plastic bit to reveal the sticky side.
把塑料放进厕所里 把它冲掉
Put the plastic bit in the bog. Flush it.
然后回去会议室 坐下来 满脸笑容
Then go back into the boardroom,
把窃听器装到桌子下面
sit down big smiles plant the bug underneath the table.
轻而易举 不费力气
Easy peasy Japanesey.
就是这样 就这么简单
Bob's your uncle. That's that.
就这么简单？并不简单
-That's that? That was that was a lot. Yeah.
我…等一下
Th I've Hold on, can you just can you repeat it again?
你可不可以慢一点再说一遍 因为我…
Just a little bit slower? Because I. . .
-听着 该死的
Shh. Listen.
休伊 冷静一下 好吗？
-Fuck. Hughie, calm down, all right?
这就像《黑客帝国》那一场戏
This is like that scene in The Matrix.
你可以吞下那颗该死的红色药丸 好吗？
Now, you could take the fucking red pill, right?
下半辈子都在手淫中度过
Spend the rest of your life jacking off,
对着你的印度茶、绿拿铁之类的哭鼻子
crying into your chai tea
或者 你可以吞下蓝色的药丸
green latte, what the fuck. Or. . . you could take the blue pill.
或者那应该是红色药丸？ 反正就是吃另一颗药丸
Or is it the red pill? Anyway, take the other pill
-别再当龟孙子了 你到底要我吞哪颗药丸？
-and quit being a cunt. Which pill do you want me to take?
别再当龟孙子了 这就是我想说的
Just quit being a cunt. That's what I'm saying.
该死的 好吧
: Fuck me. Okay.
♪ ♪
先生 能请您把口袋的东西全拿出来吗？
Sir, could you empty your pockets, please?
♪ ♪
谢谢
Thank you. ♪ ♪
Um. . .
抱歉 我可以…
excuse me, can-can I, uh. . .
我可以用一下洗手间吗？
can I use your bathroom?
先说清楚 火车头的道歉并不代表
DOUG: Just to be clear, A-Train's apology
承认任何责任之类的
isn't an admission of any sort of culpability whatsoever.
你明白吗？
Do you understand?
我为你女朋友遇到的事感到遗憾 好吗？
: I'm sorry about what happened to your girlfriend, all right?
嘿 老兄 你还好吧？
Hey, dude, are you okay?
好吧
Fine.
感谢你的道歉
I appreciate the apology.
意外是难免的 对吗？
Accidents happen, right?
毕竟你当时是在拯救世界
After all, I mean, you were saving the world.
好 很好 非常感谢
Okay, great. Thank you so much. As you know,
正如你所知道的 打击犯罪者的工作永远做不完
a crimefighter's work is never done. Douglas here will handle
道格拉斯将处理剩下的文书工作 好吗？谢谢
the rest of the paperwork for you, okay? Thank you.
可以借用你们的洗手间吗？
Can I use your bathroom?
♪ ♪
搞什么啊
What the fuck?
♪ ♪
我看着他们的眼睛 脸上带着微笑
And I look him right in the eye, and I smile.
那种感觉真是太棒了
And that was awesome, man,
老兄 有机会用眼神吓倒那个混蛋
just getting to stare that asshole down.
我明白你为什么喜欢这份工作了
I get why you dig this job.
是的 这份工作有时让你有成就感 不是吗？
Yeah, you know, it has its moments, doesn't it?
你说得对 火车头去死吧
You were right. Fuck A-Train.
火车头去死吧 超级七人队去死吧
Fuck A-Train. Fuck-fuck The Seven.
他们七个人都去死吧
Fuck all. . . Seven.
布莱曼音像店
What are we, uh. . .
我们在这里干什么？
what are we doing here?
你得去上班 不是吗？
Well, you got to go to work, don't you?
是的 但是…
Yeah, but, um, I don't, uh. . .
我不…
我是说 我需要你做的事暂时就到这里 好吗？
Well, I mean, that's all I need you for right now, yeah?
是的 但我可以…
Yeah, I mean, but I-I can. . .
我可以帮你做别的事 我可以当你的技术员
I can help with other stuff, you know? I could I could be, like, your tech guy.
例如我可以在面包车里负责那个东西 说…
You know? Like, I could be in the van with the thing
“他在大堂左手边” 我可以…
and, like, you know, "He's down the hall to the left. " Like, I can. . .
是的 听着 小子 我觉得剩下的最好就交给我
Yeah, look, son, I, uh. . . I think it's best that I take it from here.
-你明白我的意思吗？ 明白 但我真的能帮忙
-You know what I mean? Yeah, but I-I can I can really help.
我知道你能帮忙 我可以搞定
I know you can help. I got it.
嘿 等一下
Oh, w Oh, hey, wait.
你见过一个混蛋撕掉4万5千美元吗？
You ever see an asshole tear up $45K?
休伊
Hughie.
你是个好人
You're a good lad.
蒂尔威尔小姐 我还拿不准你会不会给我打电话呢
Ms. Stillwell, I wasn't sure you'd call.
你这话让我不高兴 但是…
This fucking chafes, but, um. . .
我愿意把努比亚王子的价格降到2亿3千万
I'm willing to come down to $230 million for Nubian Prince.
价格很合理 玛德 谢谢
That's very reasonable, Maddie. Thank you.
史蒂夫 那个五号化合物的事
And, Steve, this, um, Compound V,
你可能听到过的 任何关于我的英雄的谣言
any rumors you may have heard about my heroes--
是诽谤 完全是诬陷
libelous and completely untrue.
但我们都知道谣言传播很快 所以…
But we all know how rumors spread, so. . . I'd appreciate your discretion.
我希望你能守口如瓶
当然了 我向你保证
Of course. You have my word.
谢谢 一路平安
Thank you. Have a safe flight home.
监管城市本身就是个够棘手的问题 但是允许超级英雄
Policing cities is a thorny enough issue as it is,
进入国家防御系统？
but allowing superheroes into national defense?
我们基本上就是在让战争私有化
We'd basically be privatizing war.
晚安 休伊
Good night, Hughie.
你锁门好吗？
You'll lock up?
-好 行
-Yeah. Yeah.
谢谢 加里
Thanks, Gary.
抱歉 我们要打烊了
Sorry, we're closing up.
有人吗？
Hello?
你是谁？
TRANSLUCENT: Who are you?
搞什么鬼！
The fuck?
就在你面前 你这个混蛋
TRANSLUCENT: Right in front of you, prick.
你以为我找不到这个东西吗？
You think I wouldn't find this thing?
休伊
Hughie.
你这个娘炮 我从那座该死的塔就一直跟着你
You pussy, I followed you from the fucking Tower.
不
No, no, no!
跟你一起那个人是谁？在车里那个？
Who's that guy you were with, in the car?
他是谁？是他让你干这事的？
-Who was he? ! I don't. . . He put you up to this? I don't know!
我不知道 他就是个优步车司机 好吗？
He was just some Uber driver, okay?
别骗我他是优步车司机了
Don't give me some bullshit! Uber driver!
你以为我是个白痴吗？
Do you think I'm a fucking idiot?
你为什么要装窃听器？
-Why'd you plant the bug? Please.
求你了 不要 求求你
Please, please, please. No, please.
我们是超级七人队 世界上最强大的人 无辜之人的捍卫者
TRANSLUCENT: We're The Seven, Earth's most mighty,
champions of the innocent,
杂种！
motherfucker!
抱歉弄得乱七八糟的
Sorry about the mess.
你该滚了 休伊
You should fuck off, Hughie.
休伊 快跑！
Hughie, run!
哎哟喂
Well, well, well,
不就是那个隐形龟孙子嘛
if it ain't the invisible cunt.
-♪ London calling to the faraway towns ♪
♪ Now war is declared ♪
♪ And battle come down ♪
♪ London calling to the underworld ♪
♪ Come out of the cupboard, you boys and girls ♪
There you are.
-♪ London. . . ♪
那你是谁？
TRANSLUCENT: So who are you?
一个该死的间谍？
Fucking spy?
替谁当间谍？
For who? Huh?
你他妈的告诉我
You're gonna fucking tell me,
否则我就把你的脑袋砸得粉碎！
or I'm gonna smash your fucking scalp off!
你到底是谁？
Who the fuck are you? !
我来告诉你你是谁
I'll tell you who you are.
该死的蠢材
A fucking moron.
半透明并不是隐形的意思
"Translucent" doesn't even mean "invisible. "
半透明不是完全透明
It means "semi-transparent. "
他…死了吗？
Is he. . . is he dead?
-Is he. . .
他不动了
Well, he ain't moving.
糟了
Oh, fuck. Oh, shit.
你怎么知道电流能对付他？
How'd you know the electric could do the job?
他的皮肤含碳素 传导性很强
Skin's carbon. Highly conductive.
在《吉米法伦今夜秀》看到的
Saw it on, uh, Jimmy Fallon.
我可能永远都想不到这个办法
Would've taken me forever to work that one out.
干得好 把他弄到后备箱吧
Good job. Let's get him in the boot.
等等 什么？
Wait, wait, what? Wait, what? What?
-车尾箱！ 不
The trunk.
我是说我们该怎么处理他？
No, no, I mean, what are we what are we what are we doing with him?
休伊 你刚刚干掉了超级七人队之一 伙计
Well, Hughie, you just offed one of The Seven, mate.
我？我…是你开车撞了他
Me? I You-you hit him with a fucking car!
听着 你这个大脑进水的笨蛋 我们俩都惹上大麻烦了
Look, potato, fucking po-tah-to. We're both in a shitload of trouble.
不 我们没有
No, no, no, we're not! It's It--
是他攻击我的 好吧？
He-he attacked us, okay?
而你是联邦调查员 你知道吗？
And you're-you're a federal officer, you know?
你就打给该死的联调局
Just-just call the fucking FBI.
好的 好吧 听好了 严格来说我不是联调局的
Yeah, o-okay, so, look, technically, I'm not a Fed.
什么？
What? !
那你到底是什么人？
Then who the fuck are you? !
别担心 孩子 不过是气流
Don't worry about it, kiddo. It's just a little turbulence.
不会有事的
It'll be okay.
♪ Oh, the passenger. . . ♪
: Whoa.
爸爸！
Dad. Dad. Dad!
他在外面干什么？
What's he doing out here?
你们不是朋友吗？
Are you guys friends? ♪ He sees the winding ocean drive ♪
♪ And everything was made ♪
-♪ For you and me ♪ Oh, my God.
♪ All of it was made for you and me ♪
♪ 'Cause it just belongs to you and me ♪
♪ So let's take a ride and see what's mine ♪
♪ Singin' la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la, la-la ♪
♪ Oh, the passenger ♪
♪ He rides and he rides ♪
♪ He sees things from under glass ♪
♪ He looks through his window's eye ♪
♪ He sees the things he knows are his ♪
♪ He sees the bright and hollow sky ♪
♪ He sees the city asleep at night ♪
♪ He sees the stars are out tonight ♪
♪ And all of it is yours and mine ♪
♪ So let's ride and ride and ride and ride ♪
♪ Singin' la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la, la-la ♪
♪ Singin' la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la, la-la ♪
♪ Singin' la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la. . . ♪